Washington Women's Arts Center 004
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Washington Women's Arts Center Records
1972-1988
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Washington Women's Art Center
004
52 Linear feet
117 Boxes
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were donated in 1989 by Marcia Pemberton and Pamela Brown, members of the Washington Women's Arts Center.
Arrangement
Series 1: Historical Materials, 1972-1979 (1 linear ft.) This series contains correspondence and financial documents relating to the 1972 Women's Conference in the Visual Arts. The series also contains correspondence and items on the Center's first location, publicity, proposals, and studies to establish the Center.
Series 2: Board of Directors, 1974-87 (1.75 linear ft.) This series contains the Center's Board of Directors meeting minutes, annual reports, incorporation papers, by-laws, and projected budgets from 1978 through 1987.
Series 3: Office Files, 1976-1986 (3.75 linear ft.) This series contains correspondence, memoranda, brochures, press releases, and reports on government and foundation grants, publicity, elections, Center workshops, the Lansburgh Center move, and the Edith C. Blum lecture series.
Series 4: Financial Records, 1975-1978 (13.5 linear ft.) This series contains correspondence, budgets, ledgers, receipts, insurance policies, financial statements, gallery cash daybook, and other financial information. Also included are grant materials from the D.C. Government and the National Education Association.
Series 5: Membership and Guest books, 1977-1987 (1.25 linear ft.) This series contains records on individuals who supported and attended the Center's activities, including membership directories, guest books for Center events, an address book (1980), card index of active members (1987), and cards index of inactive members (1988).
Series 6: Newsletters, 1975-1981 (2.5 linear ft.) This series contains copies of the Center's newsletter "WWAC News."
Series 7: Exhibitions Files, 1975-1988 (22.5 linear ft.) This series contains materials, which document the preparation and publicity for exhibitions at the Center. Materials are arranged under three subseries.
Subseries 1: Office files, 1975-1988 (5.5 linear ft.) This series contains exhibition correspondence, handwritten lists, contracts, clippings, publicity, some photographs, and resumes.
Subseries 2: Notebooks, 1977-1985 (14.5 linear ft.) This series contains loose-leaf notebooks of documentation on exhibits. The notebooks contain photographs, correspondence, resumes, lists of items in exhibitions, slides, and clippings from the publications.
Subseries 3: Exhibition catalogs and programs, 1976-1987 (3 linear ft.) This series contains exhibit catalogs and programs from the Center and other institutions. Series 8: Audiovisual, 1972-1989 (.5 linear ft.) This series contains slides, videocassettes, audiocassettes, and photographs of exhibits, performances, and other events at the Center.
Series 9: Memorabilia, undated (.25 linear ft.) This series contains a textile banner and framed items from the Center's offices as well as miscellaneous publications from other arts organizations.
Biographical / Historical
The creation of the Washington Women's Arts Center was inspired by The Conference of Women in the Visual Arts held April 20-22, 1972 at the Corcoran Gallery; and Womansphere, an arts festival held at Glen Echo Park, Maryland in 1974. The Conference attracted significant women artists from around the country, including Elaine deKooning, Katherine Anne Porter, Lois M. Jones, and Judy Chicago. The conference steering committee consisted of Mary Beth Edelson, Cynthia Bickley-Green, Barbara Frank, Enid Sandford, Susan Sollins, Josephine Withers, and Yvonne Wulf. Participants were concerned about the presentation and involvement of so few women artists in the Corcoran's Biennial Exhibition and other exhibitions at major American art galleries. As a result of these events, local women who attended began discussing and planning for a D.C. women's arts center.
The Center was established in 1975 to provide a place for D.C. women to show their work, improve their artistic skills, and network. The original founders were Barbara Frank, Katherine Butler, Janis Goodman, Sarah Hyde, and Ann Slayton-Leffler. The site of the first Center was a basement space at 1821 Q Street, NW. The Center sponsored a monthly series of lectures and published the journal, Womansphere. The Center also conducted workshops, held literary readings, live performances, and gallery talks. The primary concentration of the Center was sponsoring juried exhibits of local women artists. In 1983 the Center moved to the Lansburgh Cultural Center located on E Street between 7th and 8th Streets, NW. In 1986 the Center changed its name to the New Arts Center and relocated to the Takoma Park neighborhood. With the new name and in an effort to increase membership, the Center began allowing male artists to join. Despite this change the Center continued to pay homage to its femist past. Financial issues force the Center to dissolve in December of 1988.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains administrative files including correspondence, board meeting minutes, annual reports, contracts, insurance policies, and grant files. The records document the Center's history and membership through guest books, membership directories, and documentation of the 1972 Women's Conference in the Visual Arts. The collection includes the Center's journal Womensphere and issues of its newsletter. Additionally, the collection contains information on the activities of the Center such as exhibits, exhibition lists, artist resumes, printed programs, and publicity materials; as well as audio and video recordings, slides, and photographs of events and exhibits. Also included are budgets, receipts, ledgers, financial statements, deposit sheets, and cash books.
Arts; Associations, institutions, etc; Women; Artists; Exhibitions; Art centers; Takoma Park (Washington, D.C.); Dupont Circle (Washington, D.C.); Pennsylvania Quarter (Washington, D.C.)
- Series 1: Historical Materials, 1972-1979
  Scope and Contents
  Correspondence and financial documents relating to the Women's Conference in the Visual Arts of 1972. Also contains correspondence and other items regarding the first site location, early publicity, proposals, and studies to establish the Center.
  - Correspondence Speakes Conference at Corcoran, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Finances Conference, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Paid Bills- Invoices, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Manuscripts, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Films and Filmmakers, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - WWAC "Q" St Floor Plans, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Adopt-Downtown Building and Space Group, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Early History, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Conference For Women Artists Pre WWAC- Correspondence, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - WWAC History: Proposals and Studies, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Programs of WWAC, 1970s (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Case Study.., 1979 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - First Press Release on WWAC and Womansphere, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - ERA March Pictures, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Women's Group- Art- Ext., Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - WWAC Puporicity Past, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Publicity and Photos for WWAC History, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - WWAC Loose Leaf Books, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Misc- Early History, Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Vinnie Ream, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Series 2: Board of Directors, 1974-87
  Contains the Center's Board of Directors meeting minutes, annual reports, incorporation papers, and by-laws of the Center. Projected budgets from 1978 through 1987 are also among the records.
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Board Minutes, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Board Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Board Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Board Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Board Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Board Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Board Minutes, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Board Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Board Minutes, 1985-1987 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Budgets, September 1978-August 1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Budget- Financial, 1982-1984 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Project Budget, 1978-1987 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Annual Reports, 1976-1983 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Annual Reports, 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Annual Meeting, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Annual Meeting, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Incorporation Papers, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - WWAC Board of Directors, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Exhibition Committee, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - WWAC Bylaws, Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Bylaws, Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Contribution to NAC, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Coalition of Women's Art Organization Membership, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Donations to NAC, 1985-1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - WWAC Board of Directors Bylaws, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors/ Membership Directors, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Series 3: Office Files, 1976-1986
  This series contains correspondence, memoranda, brochures, press releases, and reports regarding such topics as government and foundation grants, publicity, elections, Center workshops, the Lansburgh Center move, and the Edith C. Blum lecture series.
  - General Correspondence, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence- Secretary, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence- Executive Director, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence of Lucy Blackstein, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence- People We've Helped- Answered Questions, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - T. Rice- Peirera, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Election Material- Annual Meeting, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Election, 1977-1983 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Elections, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Election Ballots, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Abramson and Oronski- Probono Counsel, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Arts D.C. Participant, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - CETA Proposal, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - NEA Newsletter Grant Proposal, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - NEA Newsletter Grant, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - NEA Newsletter Grant, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - NEA Grant Application, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - NEA Public Affairs, Undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Application Copy for Charitable Solicitation License, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Government, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Maryland- Department of Employment Training- Unemployment Insurance, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Workers Compensation Insurance Info, Undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - W-2 Forms: Managing Directors; W-3 Forms: Pay, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Publicity WWAC Received, 1977-1979 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - WWAC Publicity- Misc., 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Publicity about WWAC News, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Public Relations Mailing List: Master- Labels, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Press Releases: General NAC, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Paul Levy Info: New Logo Designs, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - WWAC Brochures- History: Explanation of Center, 1976-1985 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Promo Materials, Undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Basic Publicity, Undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - WWAC Mechanicals: Brochure; Membership App; Gallery Coordinator Job Description; Sales Policy; Workshop; Sales Receipt; Payment Request, Undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Stationary Letterhead Mechanicals- Q ST/ 7TH ST, Undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Brochures, Undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Visit of Racquel De Von Vacano- U.S. Info Agency International Visitor Program, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - CETA/ Arts D.C., 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - CETA (Proposal to Arts- Arts Center), August 18 1978 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Library Correspondence, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Workshops- Fall, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Workshops, 1975-1983 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Spring Workshops, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Spring Publicity, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Spring Workshop/ Summer Workshop- Publicity- Back, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Fall Workshop Info Sheet, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Washington Women's Art Center: Summer Workshops, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Financial Statements, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Budget Projections, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Workshops, 1981-1984 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Instructors Lists, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Course Descriptions and Long Resumes, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Balance Sheets, 1976-1979 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Information Sheets/Winter, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Spring Portrait Articles, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Summer Workshops, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Summer Workshops, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Fall Workshops: Administration, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Workshop: "No Limits for Women Artists"- Betsy Damon, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Lansburgh Building, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Lansburgh Lease, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - WWAC Lansburgh Leases, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Lansburgh Workshop Space Leases, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Lansburgh CC Correspondence, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Lansburgh Building, 1980-1986 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Lansburgh's Cultural Center, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Lansburgh Building, Undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - WWAC Workshops Program: Brochures, Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - WWAC Blum Lecture Scenes- Misc., Undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Interns, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Institute of Museum Services Special Project Report, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - WWAC Executive Director- Rep. of Int.- Festival of Women Artists, July 1980 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Art and the Aging, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Student- Teacher Show, Undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Past Open Critique Flyers, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Speakers: Feminist - For Possible Lecture Series, 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Noontime Reading Series- Q ST, Undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Business for the Arts Cultural Alliance, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Cultural Alliance, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - April Trust, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Meyer Foundation Grant Application, 1975, 1978, 1982, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Time Inc./ Washington Star Grant Application, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Models Registry, Undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Newsletter: Photo Half-Tones, Undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Gallery Sutter's Book, October 1984 - April 1986 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - MCI, Undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - National Association of Artists Organizations- Artists Advocacy, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - PADC (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Payment Request- Master, Undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Small Business Administration: Financial and Staffing Report of WWAC, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Visitors to WWAC, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Volunteer Recruitment, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Stationary Logo, Undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Washington Council of Agencies, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - WPA, Undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - WWAC Founders Resumes, Undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Women's Caucus for Art, Undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - PA Ave. Working Women's Fair, May 17-18 1986 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Xerox, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Calendars, Undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Fact Sheet, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Series 4: Financial Records, 1975-1978
  This series contains correspondence, budgets, ledgers, receipts, insurance policies, financial statements, gallery cash daybook, and other financial information. The records also cover grants from the D.C. Government and the National Education Association.
  - Bank Finances Correspondence, Undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Grants Applied For, 1982-1984 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - WWAC- Various Papers Accompanying, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - WWAC- Bills to be Paid, 1980-1983 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Sales Tally Sheets, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - IMS Grant, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Contracts- Direct Sales Agreement, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - FY Annual Financial Statement (9/1/85- 8/31/86), 1985 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Misc. Fund Raising Material, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Fundraising Suggestion, Undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Goodwill Ball Donation, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Grant Fundraising, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Financial Statement, 1975-1980 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Fundraising: Year Summary, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Hechinger Funds, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Pepco - Rent - Washington Gas and Light, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Articles, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Fundraising, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Star Resumes, Undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Letters Requesting Donations, 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Mark Griffith- Women's National bank, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Giant Food Fund, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Foundation center, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Fannie Mae, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Shannon Luchs, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Mailing List, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - D.C. Humanities Council, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Legal- Name Change and Acct. 6 Period Change, 1978 and 1986 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Ainsley Wallace's Papers Re: Budget, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Budgets, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Budgets, 1984- 1986 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Budget Ideas, 1975-1977 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Budget and IRS Determination Letter, Undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Description of Exhibition Budget for 1985, Undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Stipends: K. Bahnsen; S. Snowden; J. De Vou; B. Yancey; J. Benderson, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Government, 1976-1978 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Printmakers Calendar Sales- Rec., FY 1984 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Donations, Undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - WWAC Financial Records Files- C.I.T. Financial Services, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Commission on the Arts letter, Undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Financial Forms, Undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Tax Guide- Info, Undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Income Tax Exemption Letters, Undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Tax Exempt Certificates for D.C. Sales Tax, Undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - 2758 Tax Form, Undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Sales Tax, 1982-1988 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Taxes (Sales), Undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Employee ID Number- Personal Property Tax (1099), Undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Spare Tax Forms: W-2, Undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - IRS Tax Exempt, Undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Copies of Tax Exempt Status- Certificate of Exemption D.C., Undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - 941- 941E, Undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - 990 Form Submissions, FY 1985 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - 990 Filed 1-10-1985, FY 1984 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - 990, Undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - 1099 Misc. Income Forms, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Tax Instructions: Fed, Undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - W-4 Form for Employees, Undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Notes and Correspondent Taxes, Undated (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Exemption Forms and Exemption, Undated (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Private Foundation Status for IRS, Undated (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Interest on Bank Deposits- Women's National Bank, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Tax Info- Perpetual American Bank, Jan- Dec 1985 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - D.C. Exemption from Franchise Tax and Non-profit Filing, Undated (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - D.C. Combined Registration Application- To Pay our own Workmans Comp, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Income Stub-Current, Undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Lansburgh Rent and Expenses, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Calvert Group, Undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Apple Grant, Undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Community Foundation, Undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - C and P Phone Funding, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Financial Consultant Info- Mr. Goodwin Emeritus Foundation, Undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Huntington Block Insurance, Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Insurance Policies, 1975-1978 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Exhibition Insurance, 1978-1980 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Huntington T. Block- Insurance at WWAC, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Insurance- Fine Art- Huntington T. Block, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Insurance- Fine Art- Huntington T. Block, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Insurance- Fine Art- Huntington T. Block, Undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Insurance- Fine Art- Huntington T. Block, Undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Insurance- Fine Art- Huntington T. Block, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Insurance- Fine Art- Huntington T. Block, 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Huntington T. Block, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Insurance Correspondence, March 1976- July 1978 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Insurance Correspondence, September 1978- 1980 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Insurance Forms for Exhibits- Alt Specs, Undated (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Insurance (For Freelance Artists, Undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Insurance- Liability - Workers Comp, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Insurance- Liability - Workers Comp, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Insurance- Liability - Workers Comp, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Insurance- Liability- Workers Comp, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Special- Bins, Undated (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Insurance- Liability- Workers Comp, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Huntington T. Block Insurance, Undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Insurance- Alt Sp, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Grant "City Spirit", 1975 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - NEA Intern Program, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - NEA Grant, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - NEA Grant, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - NEA Grant, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - ProFemina- NEA Grant, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - NEA Slide Region, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - NEA Summer Intern Program, Fall 1978 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - NEA Photography Publications Grant Proposal, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - NEA Grant Photography, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - NEA Grant for Exhibitions, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - NEA Grant, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Grants, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Institute of Museum Scores- Copy of Grant Papers, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Institute of Museum Services, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - IMS and M.A.P. Grants, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - NEA Grant For 1983, 8/84 -7/85 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - NEA Funding, 1984-1985 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - NEA Grant Application, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - NEA Grant Application, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - NEA, 1985-1987 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - NEA Grant Application, 1986-1987 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - NEA Grant Application, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - NEA Guidelines, 1988 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Advertising Space, Undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Commission on Arts and Humanities Grant, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Commission on Arts and Humanities Grant Mated, 1977-1978 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Commission on Arts and Humanities Grants Material, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Commission on Arts and Humanities Grants, 1979-1980 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Government Grant, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Commission Five-Year Plan, March 1981 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Government Grants, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Commission on Arts and Humanities (Alt. Sp) Grant, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Grant Proposal to Commission on Arts and Humanities, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Commission Special Constituencies, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Commission Grant, July 1 1978- June 30 1980 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Arts D.C./ CETA Proposal, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Arts D.C./ CETA Proposal, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Commission, FY 1984 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Commission Annual Report, 1984-1985 (Box 27, Folder 2)